（サテラ）
もう一度 聞くわ
I'll ask you one more time.
Why did you call me by the name
of the Witch of Envy?
どうして 私を
嫉妬の魔女の名で呼ぶの？
（ナツキ･スバル）
だって そう呼べって…
Because I was told to.
I don't know who told you that,
（サテラ）
誰に言われたか知らないけど
趣味が悪すぎる
but they have terrible taste!
禁忌(きんき)の象徴 嫉妬の魔女
口にするのも はばかられる―
The Witch of Envy is the epitome of taboo,
and you call me by her name,
which most dare not even say!
そんな名で呼ぶなんて
（男Ａ）そうだそうだ
That's right!
You went too far, man!
（男Ｂ）
あんまりだぞ 兄ちゃん
用がないなら行くわ
私も暇じゃないから
If you have nothing to say, I'm leaving.
I have things to do.
（フェルト）フヒッ
Felt!
フェルト あっ
このための足止め？
あなたもグル？
Were you stalling me?
Are you working with her!?
N-No!
ち… 違う！
Hey... W-Wait a minute!
あっ おい 待… ちょっと待て！
It's not like that! I'm...
誤解だ 俺は…
Damn it!
クソッ
Would it kill someone to be nice to me?
誰か もっと俺に優しくしろよ
Why was I even...
何のための…
summoned to this world?
異世界召喚だよ
What are you rambling about?
（カン）
てめえ 何 ブツブツ言ってんだ？
If you don't wanna get hurt,
cough up whatever you've got!
（チン）
痛(いて)え思いしたくなきゃ―
出すもん 出しな
フッヒヒヒヒ
Buzz off already!
いいかげんにしろよ！
（３人）ん？
No one is this damn persistent!
性懲りもないにも
程があるだろうが
You think you can mouth off to us!?
なんだ その態度は！
Just go away!
ジャマだ
I have somewhere else I need to be!
俺は 行かなきゃならない所が
あるんだよ
（トン）
ああ… やっちまった
Man, now you've done it.
You seriously stabbed him?
You've gotta be kidding me...
（スバル）
冗談じゃねえ 痛え 痛い…
Ow... It hurts...
N-No! He just walked into my blade!
ガハッ
What are you doing?
何やってんだ お前
I-It's already done!
（カン）
もったいねえだろ！
何か 何か金めの物でも…
Just take anything worth selling!
（スバル）あれ…
Huh?
Now's not the time!
The guards will be here any second!
But Old Man Rom ate those.
（スバル）
ロム爺(じい)に食われたはず… なんでだ
How?
C-Could... this be...
これは
ひょっとして…
Run! We're in trouble!
（チン）逃げろ ヤバイ！
Well, bud? You want this appa?
（カドモン･リッシュ）
兄ちゃん リンガは？
なあ おっちゃん
Hey, mister...
Huh?
How many times have you seen me now?
俺の この顔見るのって何度目？
What do you mean?
I've never seen you before.
何回も何も 初めてだろうが
Come on, bud.
Are you buying it or not?
兄ちゃん リンガは？
Sorry, but I'm broke beyond compare!
悪(わり)いけど 天壌無窮の一文無し
（カドモン）
とっとと失せろー！
Get the hell outta here!
Wallet, cell phone,
corn potage snack, cup noodles.
（スバル）
財布 携帯 コンポタにカップ麺
My tracksuit and sneakers are intact too.
ジャージとスニーカーも
ほころびナッシング
そして 当然…
And naturally...
Thank god. A wound to the back
is a warrior's greatest shame.
よかったぜ 背中の傷とか
マジ 剣士の恥だかんな
Well, with so much circumstantial
evidence, there's no denying it.
さて こんだけ状況証拠がそろうと
認めるしかねえか
It's kinda hard to believe,
but it has to be that.
ちょい信じがたいことだけど
つまり あれだな
A time leap.
タイムリープ
しかも―
And each time, I return to my initial state.
死ぬたびに 初期状態に戻る
I'll call it
名付けて―
"Return by Death."
死に戻り
I actually get a time-leap ability,
and it only activates when I die.
せっかくの
タイムリープ能力なのに―
死ななきゃ発動しないって
負け犬前提が いかにも俺らしい
That pathetic precondition suits me perfectly.
If I've gone back in time,
Satella hasn't saved me in this fourth life.
（スバル）
時間をさかのぼったってことは
この４度目の世界じゃ
サテラは俺を助けてない
Meaning the debt I owed her for that is gone.
つまり 返すべき恩義も
きれいさっぱり
なくなっちまったってことだ
In that case, I should forget everything, sell this,
だったら 全部忘れちまって
とっとと これ売っぱらって―
save some funds, and use my knowledge
of the modern world to live in luxury!
軍資金作って 現代知識で
異世界ウハウハライフだ
A dream is unfolding before my very eyes!
夢が広がるぜ
（店主）ん？
（スバル）なあ おっさん
Right, mister?
Wh-Why are you asking me?
な… 何だね 急に
I have no idea what you're talking about.
“なあ”とか言われても
知らないよ 私は
Aw, that's cold...
なんだよ 冷てえなあ
I don't wanna get caught up
in other people's problems.
（店主）
よそ者の面倒ごとに
関わるのはごめんだよ
Don't talk to me.
話かけないでおくれ
Well, I guess "Let sleeping dogs lie" goes in any world.
（スバル）
まあ どこの世界でも
触らぬ神にたたりなしってのは
一緒か
But still, there are always softies
でもよ
自分が切羽詰まってでも―
人のこと助けちまう
お人好しもいるんだよなあ
who help others, even when
they really can't afford to...
She'd just had something precious stolen.
大切な物を盗まれて
それどころじゃないってのに―
She didn't have time for me.
Yet she saved some useless stranger,
無関係の役立たずを助けて
治療までしてやって―
and even healed him.
Then she played along with
that useless stranger's self-satisfaction.
そんでもって その役立たずの
自己満足につきあって…
Even if Satella doesn't know me,
（スバル）
たとえ サテラが
俺と知り合ってなくても
Felt still stole her insignia. And Elsa will...
フェルトは徽章(きしょう)を盗み
そして エルザの奴が…
No matter how many times
I repeat this, that won't change.
そこんとこは
何度繰り返しても変わらない
They say history repeats itself, right?
歴史の強制力ってやつか
Yeah.
やっぱ―
If I'm aware that people I used to
know are going to be killed,
いっぺん知り合った奴らが
殺されるって分かってて―
見過ごすのは無理だ！
I can't just ignore it!
ハア ハア…
Hey, mister...
（スバル）
なあ おっちゃん
What do you want, broke kid?
なんだ？ 一文無し
There's something I want to ask you...
（スバル）
ちょっと 聞きたいんだけど―
Have there been any pickpocketing
incidents around here?
この辺で
スリ騒ぎとかなかったか？
Asking questions without buying anything?
You really do have guts.
何も買わずに質問とか
いい度胸してんな
Incidents like that aren't uncommon at all.
そんな騒ぎなんか
珍しくも何ともねえよ
Though, that last one was unusual...
だが さっきのは珍しかったなあ
They threw some magic around
in the street a few times.
通りで２ ３度 魔法がぶっ放された
Things that looked like icicles
flew around and lodged in the wall.
つららが矢みたいに飛んで
突き刺さった跡だ
They didn't last too long, though.
すぐに消えちまったがな
I'm too late?
（スバル）出遅れたか
I thought if I could keep the insignia
from being stolen, then maybe...
徽章が盗まれるのを阻止すれば
ひょっとしてと思ったけど…
Maybe what?
何が“ひょっとして”だ？
Oh, just talking to myself, but...
ああ こっちの話だ　だけど―
Thanks, mister.
ありがとな おっちゃん
何も買ってないのに教えてくれてよ
You told me even though I didn't buy anything.
It's no big deal.
（カドモン）
たいしたこっちゃねえ
Someone just as broke as you helped
my daughter after she got lost earlier.
ついさっき
あんたと同じ無一文に―
迷子の娘が
助けられたばっかりなんでな
Fate has a funny way of doing things...
これも運命の強制力 か…
What are you smiling about?
（カドモン）
何 笑ってやがる
Nothing.
（スバル）何でもねえ
I'll buy an appa next time!
次は きっと
リンガ買わせてもらうよ
Sure. Buy one, and you'll be a customer.
ああ 買うならお客様だ
Get to work, broke kid!
働けよ 無一文！
Right!
（スバル）おう
There's only one thing to do now!
（スバル）
こうなりゃ 方法は１つだ
Before Elsa comes to the loot house,
エルザが盗品蔵に行く前に―
I have to buy the insignia from Felt,
and return it to Satella!
フェルトから徽章を買い取って
サテラに返す
Wait...
いや サテラってのは
偽名だったんだろうな
Satella was just an alias, wasn't it?
Then I've gotta get her
to tell me her real name this time—
んだらば 今度は名前くらい―
ちゃーんと教えてもらえるように
頑張らないと
What are you rambling about?
てめえ 何 ブツブツ言ってんだ？
If you don't wanna get hurt,
cough up whatever you've got!
痛え思いしたくなきゃ
出すもん出しな
I'm getting sick of seeing your faces,
Larry, Moe, and Curly.
もう いいかげんに お前らの顔も
見飽きたぜ トンチンカン
After doing this four times,
I've learned my lesson!
こっちも４度目となりゃ
学習してんだ
Guards!
衛兵さーん！
What the hell, you bastard!?
てめえ ふざけんなよ！
My memory from before was right.
（スバル）
やはり あん時の記憶は正しかった
This world does have some kind of police force!
この世界にも 警察機構的な
存在があるってことだ
Someone! P-Please, I need a man!
（スバル）
誰か！ ハアッ 男の人呼んでー
Damn it, shut up!
（チン）
ざけんな 黙れ！
No, don't touch me! Stop!
（スバル）
ちょっと触らな… ちょっ やだ…
I can't hear you!
Say it like you mean it!
聞こえない
誠意が足んなくて聞こえない
Help me, officer!
お巡りさーん…
Huh?
あれ？
Don't scare me like that.
脅かしやがって
I might have freaked out, just a little.
ほんの少しだけ？
ビビっちまったじゃねえか
Just a little bit.
ほんの少しだけ？
Just a tiny, little bit.
ほんのちょびっとだけど？
Running won't save you now.
逃げようったってムダだぜ
That's enough.
（男）そこまでだ
（トン）赤髪に―
Red hair.
And a knight's sword marked by scratches from dragon claws.
龍の爪跡の刻まれた 騎士剣
Seriously?
まさか ラインハルト…
Reinhard?
The Sword Saint, Reinhard?
剣聖 ラインハルトか？
Seems I needn't introduce myself.
（ラインハルト･
ヴァン･アストレア）
自己紹介の必要はなさそうだ
Although that nickname is a bit much.
もっとも その２つ名は
僕には まだ重すぎる
I don't know how much my
modest strength could aid him.
僕の微力が どれだけ
彼の助けになるか分からないが―
But if you wish to resort to extreme measures,
もしも
強行手段に出るというなら―
as a knight, I would have to retaliate.
騎士として あらがわせてもらうよ
冗談じゃねえ 割に合わねえよ！
Screw this! It's not worth it!
I'm glad we're both safe. Are you unhurt?
お互い無事でよかった
ケガはないかい？
A-Allow me to thank you from
the bottom of my heart for saving my life!
ここ… この度は 命を救って頂き
心から お礼を申し上げる
I, Natsuki Subaru,
deeply admire your selflessness!
このナツキ･スバル―
そのお心の清廉さに
感服致しますれば…
No need for such formality.
そんなに
かしこまらなくてもかまわないよ
They only lost their advantage
because it was two on three.
向こうも３対２になって―
優位性を
確保できなくなってのことだ
It wouldn't have gone so well if I'd been alone.
僕１人じゃ こうはいかなかった
H-His nice-guy index is off the charts.
（スバル）
何だ？ この爽やか指数…
えーと…
Uh... Reinhard-san, right?
ラインハルトさん…
でいいんすか？
You may just call me Reinhard, Subaru.
呼び捨てでかまわないよ スバル
He closed our distance like it was nothing...
（スバル）
さらっと距離詰めてきたな
Well, thanks again, Reinhard.
改めてありがとう ラインハルト
You're the only one who paid any
attention to my cries for help.
俺の叫びを聞いて
駆けつけてくれたの お前だけだぜ
マジ寂しい
Talk about depressing.
It's too risky for most people
to oppose people like them.
多くの人にとって―
彼らのような者と
反目するのはリスクが大きい
その点 衛兵を呼んだ
君の判断は正しかったよ
As far as it goes, you were right
to call for the guards.
Are you a guard?
（スバル）
ラインハルトって衛兵なの？
You don't look like one...
全然 そうは見えないけど…
I'm off duty today,
so I'm not in uniform.
今日は非番で
制服を着てないのもあるし―
And I realize that I don't
appear particularly intimidating.
見た目にいかつさが足りないのは
自覚しているところだけどね
Come to think of it,
didn't they call you the Sword Saint?
（スバル）
そういえば 剣聖とか
呼ばれてた気がするけど…
My family is fairly unique.
（ラインハルト）
家が少しだけ特殊でね
Every day, I feel I'll be
crushed by their expectations.
かけられた期待の重さに
潰れそうな日々だとも
Anyway, Subaru...
ところで スバル
You have quite the unusual hair, apparel, and name.
君は珍しい髪と服装
そして 名前だけど―
What nation are you from?
どこの国から？
At the moment, Lugunica is a bit more restless than in peacetime.
今のルグニカは 平時より
少し落ち着かない状況にある
If you have a problem,
I'd be glad to help you.
何か困ったことがあるなら
僕でよければ手伝うけど
Would you come to the loot house?
だったら 一緒に盗品蔵に…
（ラインハルト）盗品蔵？
The loot house?
N-Never mind... Forget it.
あっ いや… 何でもない
忘れてくれ
I can't trouble you with that...
そこまで迷惑はかけられねえ
あとは自分で何とかするさ
I'll handle the rest on my own somehow.
けど １つ伝言を
頼まれてくれるとうれしい
But...
I'd appreciate it if you could deliver a message.
Of course. I'd be glad to.
もちろん喜んで
誰に 何を伝えればいい？
To whom? And what?
Well, I don't know her name, but...
（スバル）
ああ… 俺も名前は
知らないんだけど―
Have you seen a girl with white robes
and silver hair nearby?
この辺りで 白いローブを着た
銀髪の女の子を見なかった？
White robes and silver hair?
白いローブに銀髪…
She's also extremely gorgeous!
付け加えると 超絶美少女
No, I haven't.
いや 見なかったなあ
Then, if you do see her,
（スバル）
じゃあ もし見かけたら―
tell her not to go near
the loot house, no matter what.
何があっても 盗品蔵には
近づくなって伝えてくれ
I'll find what she's looking
for and bring it to her myself.
捜し物は 必ず この俺が見つけて
届けるからって
Very well. If I see her,
I shall relay your message.
（ラインハルト）分かった
もし その女性に出会ったら
必ず伝えよう
Thanks.
ありがとう
I'll repay you one day!
この礼は いずれ
All right.
Take care.
気をつけて
Felt's den?
（男）
フェルトの奴のねぐらか？
Yeah, just go two streets down that way.
そんなら そこの通りを
２本奥に行った先だ
Thanks, I appreciate it, bro.
（スバル）
ありがとう 助かったよ兄弟
Don't mention it, bro. Live strong.
気にすんなよ兄弟
強く生きろよ
The real question is if she'll return there.
問題は フェルトが
戻ってくるかだな
I'd rather catch her before she goes to the loot house,
できれば盗品蔵に
フェルトが入る前につかまえて―
and trade her the cell phone for the insignia—
携帯と徽章を
交換しちまいたいところだが
Whoa!
（スバル）おっとっと…
（エルザ･グランヒルテ）あら
Oh, dear!
I'm terribly sorry. Are you all right?
ごめんなさい 大丈夫かしら？
Yeah, I'm fine.
ああ 大丈夫 大丈夫
こう見えて俺って 丈夫なのが―
I don't look it, but toughness is one thing I... have...
取り柄…
（エルザ）
ウフフ どうしたの？
What's wrong?
You don't have to be so scared.
I won't do anything to you.
そんなに怖がらなくても
何もしないのだけれど
I... I'm not scared...
こ… 怖がるとかしてねえよ
何を根拠にそんなこと…
What gave you that idea?
におい
Your scent.
When people are scared,
I can smell their fear.
怖がっている時 その人からは
怖がってるにおいがするものよ
Right now, you're frightened.
あなたは今 怖がってる
それから 怒ってもいるわね―
You're also angry, aren't you?
At me.
私に対して
ウフフ
It's fine.
いいわ
（スバル）う…
I'm a little curious, but now
isn't the time to start a commotion.
少し気になるけれど―
今は 騒ぎを起こすわけには
いかないから
That's not a very nice thing to say...
穏当じゃない発言だな
If you're too scary,
that beauty will go to waste—
あんましビビらせると
美人が台無しだぜ
Oh, very good.
あら お上手
Conceal your hostility,
and you'll be even better.
敵意を隠せば もっと上出来よ
それじゃあ 失礼するわ
Well, I'll be going now.
Something tells me we'll meet again.
また会えそうな気がするわね
ハッ ハア…
（スバル）
これ 人の住みかか？
Wow, someone actually lives here?
まさか すでにエルザが
暴れたあとって可能性はないよな
Elsa hasn't already come by
and trashed the place, right?
だ… 大丈夫だ たぶん
血のにおいはしねえ
I-It's fine, I'm sure.
I don't smell blood.
But it does smell like garbage.
生ゴミのにおいはするけど…
（フェルト）
てめえ 人んち のぞき込んで
何してんだ
What do you think you're doing
riffling around in someone else's house?
残念だが 私んちには
盗る物なんざ 何もねえ
Sorry to disappoint you,
but there's nothing worth stealing in there.
帰れ
Beat it!
ま… 待て 違う そうじゃない
No, wait! I'm not a thief.
（フェルト）
うっせえ 問答無用だ！
Shut up! Don't argue!
Whoa, stop...
（スバル）やめろ
Calm down! This is no time to fight!
落ち着け 争ってる場合じゃない
日が暮れる前に…
Before it gets dark—
（フェルト）
日が暮れる前に とっとと消えな
Before it gets dark, you'd better be gone.
I told you I'm not a thief...
（スバル）
だから そうじゃなくて…
You don't give up, do you?
しつけえな 兄ちゃん
とっとと消えろって言ってんだろ！
I told you to get out of here!
Just listen to me!
（スバル）だから 話を…
（スバル）おおっと うわ！
た… 頼む
話を聞いてくれ フェルト
P-Please! Just hear me out, Felt!
大事な用があって来たんだ
I came to see you on important business!
How do you know my name?
何で 私の名前知ってんだ
ひょっとして盗みの依頼か？
You want me to steal something for you?
だったら 最初から言えよ
You should have said that first!
いきなり 襲いかかってきたの
お前だろ
You attacked me before I could get a word in!
つーか アコギな商売しやがって
手癖の悪さが自慢か
You know, this is a greedy business you're running!
Do you pride yourself on sticky fingers?
生きる手段の問題さ
これがなきゃ 体でも売るしかねえ
You can't be picky if you wanna stay alive.
It's either this or selling my body.
で 用件って何だよ
とっとと言え
So what's your business with me?
Spit it out.
There's one thing I want.
俺の用件は１つ
お前が盗んだ徽章を
こちらで買い取りたい
I want to buy the insignia you stole here and now!
依頼人の姉さんと
あんたは別口だよな？
You aren't associated with my client.
商売仇(がたき)か 何かか？
Are you a business rival?
商売仇というか
親の仇のような相手というか―
Call her a rival, or the person who killed my parents.
むしろ 俺の仇みたいな感じ？
You could even call her
the person who killed me.
You make no sense.
分かんねえよ
Well, I'm only interested in selling it
to the highest bidder.
まあ 私としては―
買い取り価格が高いほうに
売りつけるだけだ
もうかる可能性がある話なら
なんだって聞くぜ
If you've got an offer that'll net me
some good money, I'll listen.
たくましいこった
Very shrewd...
こっちは聖金貨で 20枚以上の
価値のある物を用意してる
I have something worth
more than twenty holy coins.
その条件で
お前の徽章を買い取りたい
I want to buy your insignia with it.
これは ちまたで大流行の
ミーティアってやつだ
It's what everyone wants these days, a metia.
This is the power of a metia!
（スバル）
これがミーティアの力だ
時間を切り取って
凍結させることができる―
It's a one-of-a-kind item that can
capture a moment and freeze it in time.
世界で１つだけの貴重品
さあ どうよ？
So how about it?
ウソじゃなさそうだな
You don't seem to be lying.
But that's supposed to be me?
でも これが私か？ もっと美人だろ
I'm way prettier.
If you look this good without makeup,
you're doing fine...
ノーメイク スッピンでこれなら
上等だろ
Don't complain.
文句言ってんじゃねえ
Well, it is unusual. I'll give you that.
（フェルト）
まあ 物珍しさは認めるけどよ―
But twenty holy coins? Not likely.
聖金貨20枚ってのは眉唾だぜ？
私だって 交渉相手の言うこと
丸飲みにしてやるほど―
I'm not so stupid as to believe everything
a prospective buyer says without question.
頭からっぽってな
わけじゃねえんだ
Well, of course not.
（スバル）
そりゃまあ 当然だな
貧民街の奥に 盗品蔵がある
At the far edge of the slums is a loot house.
そこにいる ロム爺って
偏屈爺さんに―
The fair thing is to have the codger
who lives there, Old Man Rom, appraise it.
鑑定してもらうのが公平だぜ
やっぱ そうくるか
So it still comes to that...
Okay, got it. Let's go.
（スバル）
よし 分かった 行こう
すぐ行こう パッと行こう
ちゃちゃっと行こう
Right now. Let's move!
On the double!
We'll have him take a look,
and get right out of there!
ただし ちょっと見てもらって
スパッと終わらせて―
バシッと出るからな
Hey, slow down!
What's your problem?
（フェルト）
なんだよ兄ちゃん
なんで そんなに焦ってんだよ
Why are you in such a hurry?
汗ダラダラだぜ？
You're soaked with sweat.
強く生きろよ
Live strong.
Everyone in the slums says that.
貧民街だと
みんな それ言うんだけど―
何かスローガンなの？
Is it some kind of slogan?
あんな奴らと一緒にすんな
Don't lump me in with those guys!
あいつら みんな口だけで
強くも何ともねえ
They're all talk. They aren't strong at all.
性根のしみったれた
人生の負け犬どもだよ
They're just a bunch of stingy losers at life.
That's a bit harsh...
（スバル）
いくらなんでも言い過ぎだろ
私は ここにいる奴らとは違う
I'm not like the people here.
こんな路地裏で―
I have no intention of living
out my life in these back alleys!
一生を終わらせる気なんて
さらさらねえんだ
それで？
And you think twenty holy coins
will make your dream come true?
聖金貨20枚で お前の
その夢は かないそうなのかよ
目標にでっかく近づくのは
間違いねえよ
It's true that it'd be
a huge leap toward my goal.
私 １人なら―
Even if I were alone, it isn't
as if I couldn't get by with effort.
無理すりゃ やってけねえことも
ねえだろうけど
１人なら？
If you were alone?
Never mind.
（フェルト）何でもねえよ
何だよ そのにやけづら
腹立つな おい
What are you smirking about?
You really piss me off!
気にすんな
Don't worry about it.
え… ちょ ちょっ…
何すんだ やめろ！
H-Hey, what're you doing? Stop!
Hey!
うまくやんなきゃいけねえよな
Just gotta make it work, huh?
I said, "Stop!"
俺にしかできないことだ
And only I can do that.
わけ分かんねえこと言って
浸ってんじゃねえよ
Stop spewing sentimental nonsense!
噛(か)むぞ！
I'll bite you!
（スバル）
あの子のためだけじゃない
I'm not only doing it for her.
待ち受ける運命を 俺が変えてやる
I'll change the fate that's waiting for me.
そのために 俺は…
And to do that, I'll...
I told you to cut it out!
（フェルト）
いいかげんにしろっつうの！
これがミーティア
So this is a metia...
さしもの わしも
見るのは初めてじゃが…
Even I've never seen one before.
（スバル）
割とデリケートな機械だから
扱いには注意
It's fairly delicate, so handle it with care.
ぶっ壊されると マジで
死ななきゃならないレベル
Think along the lines of,
"If you break it, you'll die."
やり直し的な意味で
No do-overs.
（ロム爺）
これは 確かに恐れ入ったわい
Yeah, I'm definitely impressed.
もしも わしが取り扱うなら
聖金貨で15 いや…
If I were to sell this,
I'd take no less than fifteen—
No, twenty holy coins.
20枚は下らずにさばいてみせる
それだけの価値はある
It's worth at least that.
うっしゃー！
All right! Negotiations complete!
てなわけで 交渉成立
Now, if we're done talking, let's go
for drinks to celebrate a completed sale!
じゃあ 話は終わりとして―
これから みんなで―
商談成立の祝いに
一杯やりに行こうぜ
（フェルト）ちょっと待て
Hold it!
何で そんなに急いでんだ？
Why are you in such a hurry?
人生ってのは 有限なんだ
Life doesn't last forever.
Make every second count.
Don't waste any—
１秒１秒を大切に
ムダを極力省く…
Yeah, yeah! I don't care about all that.
（フェルト）
あー はいはい
そういうのはいいんで
つかさ そもそも何で兄ちゃんが
この徽章を欲しがんだよ
Why do you even want the insignia anyway?
この徽章は何だ？
This insignia is actually worth
a lot more than it looks, right?
実はこいつには この見た目以上の
価値があるんだろ？
だから みんな欲しがるんだ
That's why everyone wants it.
つまり こいつは―
In other words, I can get more
off this than your metia—
ミーティア以上の
金になるってこと…
Hang on, Felt!
That's a dangerous way to think!
待て フェルト
お前その考え マジに危ういぞ！
聖金貨20枚以上
その価値で手を打っとけ
He appraised it at over twenty holy coins.
Just sell it for that! Don't ask for more!
それ以上は欲しがるな！
エル… お前に依頼した奴だって
聖金貨20枚が限界だ
El— The woman who asked you
for it can't go higher than twenty either.
それ以上は出してこない
She won't pay more than that!
（フェルト）フン
何であんたが それ知ってんだよ
How do you know that?
語るに落ちてるぜ
関係者だってな
You just admitted that you're with them.
時間がないんだ　頼む フェルト
I don't have time... Please, Felt!
頼まれてもなあ
Begging won't help.
あんたを
交渉相手としては認めるよ
I acknowledge you as a negotiating party.
But not hearing what my
client says wouldn't be fair.
でも 依頼人の意見を聞かなくちゃ
フェアじゃねえ
（スバル）俺が―
The reason I want that insignia
それを欲しがるのは―
元の持ち主に返したいからだ
is so I can return it to its owner.
Huh?
俺は それを持ち主に返したい
I want to return it to its owner!
だから徽章を欲しがってる
That's why I want the insignia!
それだけだ　頼む！
That's all! So please!
フェルト どうも この小僧
ウソをついてるようには見えんが
Felt, it doesn't look to me like the boy's lying.
ロム爺までほだされんなよ
冗談に決まってんだろ
Don't get taken in by him.
He's obviously joking around.
持ち主に返す？ バカバカしい
Return it to the owner? Ridiculous!
つくなら もっと
マシなウソをつけよ
If you're gonna lie, make it believable!
私はだまされねえ！
I won't be fooled!
フェルト…
Felt...
誰じゃ？
Who's that?
（フェルト）
私の客かもしんねえ
It might be for me.
It's a little early, though.
まだ 早い気がするけど
（スバル）開けるな！
（フェルト）ん？
Don't open it!
殺されるぞ
W-We'll be killed!
Kill you? I wouldn't do something so terrifying.
殺すとか そんな おっかないこと
いきなりしたりしないわよ
Reunion with the   Witch
oh,
please
don't
let
me
die
Reunion with the   Witch
oh,
please
Reunion with the   Witch
oh,
please
Reunion with the   Witch
don't
let
Reunion with the   Witch
don't
let
me
die
wai
ting
for
your
touch
die
wai
ting
for
your
touch
no,
don't
give
up
on
life
no,
don't
give
up
on
life
this
end
less
dead
end
life
this
end
less
dead
end
ku
ru
tta
to
kei
ki
zamu
i
nochi
a defective hourglass counts my life away,
ku
ru
tta
to
kei
ki
zamu
i
nochi
ko
bo
re
te
ku
ki
ok
u
no
su
na
grains of memory spilling out
nochi
ko
bo
re
te
ku
ki
ok
u
no
su
na
me
ba
e
ta
o
moi
ma
de
ne
e
na
will the feelings I developed
me
ba
e
ta
o
moi
ma
de
ne
e
ko
n
na
ni
a
k
ke
na
ku
ki
e
te
ma
shi
u
no?
escape just as easily?
ko
n
na
ni
a
k
ke
na
ku
ki
e
te
ma
shi
u
no?
I
wish
was
there
I
wish
was
I
there
was
oh,
please
don't
let
me
die
there
oh,
please
don't
let
me
die
wai
ting
for
your
touch
die
wai
ting
for
your
touch
ni
do
to
na
ni
mo
na
ku
sa
nu
yo
u
ni
so that you'll never lose anything again,
touch
ni
do
to
na
ni
mo
na
ku
sa
nu
yo
u
ni
wa
ta
shi
wo
wa
su
re
te
ha
ji
me
te
Start"
"Re:
ni
please forget me and "Re:Start"
wa
ta
shi
wo
wa
su
re
te
ha
ji
me
te
Start"
"Re:
no,
don't
give
up
on
life
no,
don't
give
up
on
life
this
end
less
dead
end
life
this
end
less
dead
end
ki
mi
wo
ku
da
ko
no
ka
na
shi
mi
ga
I hope the sadness tearing you apart
end
ki
mi
wo
ku
da
ko
no
ka
na
shi
mi
ga
i
tsu
ka
o
wa
ri
ma
su
you
ni
will someday come to an end
i
tsu
ka
o
wa
ri
ma
su
you
ni
for
now,
I'll
see
you
off
ni
for
now,
I'll
see
you
off
and
we'll
die
wai
ting
for
a
ne
w
day
and
we'll
die
wai
ting
for
a
ne
w
day
ni
do
to
never again
day
ni
do
to
and
we'll
start
wai
ting
for
a
ne
w
day
and
we'll
start
wai
ting
for
a
ne
w
day
ki
mi
to...
together with you...
day
ki
mi
to...